<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Benjamins&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>https://benjaminpohl.tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Benjamins&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.127.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://benjaminpohl.tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://benjaminpohl.tech/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://benjaminpohl.tech/papers/</guid>
      <description>Works 📚 ML Skill Profiles: An Organizational Blueprint for Scaling Enterprise ML Contributing Partner on the Applied AI Whitepaper, facilitating the delineation of essential skill profiles for successful implementation and scaling of machine learning initiatives.
Used:
MLOps Organization 📄 Download Whitepaper
Content-based Music Recommendation (MSc. Thesis) Recent boom in the industry of digital music distribution has made recommendation systems more of a necessity than a convenience both for consumers as well as business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://benjaminpohl.tech/personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://benjaminpohl.tech/personal/</guid>
      <description>Benjamin Pohl About Me &amp;ldquo;Every challenge fuels the journey towards innovation and excellence.&amp;rdquo;
Accomplished Lead Machine Learning Engineer with over 7 years of experience in architecting and managing analytical platforms across Azure, GCP, and AWS, with a primary focus on Azure. Specializing in designing and deploying scalable machine learning models, I excel in leveraging advanced analytics to drive business insights and decision-making. Passionate about generative AI and staying ahead of emerging technologies, I am dedicated to creating innovative solutions that align with privacy and responsible AI development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://benjaminpohl.tech/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://benjaminpohl.tech/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects 🚀 Webstore for Artisan Guizhou Chili (2024) GZChilli
Created a webstore selling artisan Guizhou chili with features for product display, user reviews, and secure checkout.
Entrepreneur &amp;amp; Technical Lead (2023) VEEDUS
Development of an entire Web App with front- and backend capabilities, user management, and web-shop.
Machine Learning NLP Consulting (2020) 20Flow7
Developed an NLP algorithm to predict psychological key factors from application cover letters.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
